Amongst those who drank the elixir, it is forbidden to use false names.
Immortals will only be able to talk with each other using their real names.
We're really immortal!
I'm so moved!
I am Ennis. I don't have a last name.
Ennis... It's Ennis, right?!
I like kids who are good at complimenting.
So, what did you want?
これはこれはベリアム上院議員…
Well, well, if it isn't Senator Beriam.
ゎざゎざ面会とは光栄ですね…
I'm honored by your visit.
貴様の弟子どもが厄介なことを
しでかしてくれたのでな…
Your underlings have done some nasty things.
レムレ一スたちが何を?
What have the Lemures done?
They have stormed the transcontinental train, the Flying Pussyfoot.
大陸横断特急 フライ ング
プツシ一フッ 卜号を占拠した…
乗客の命と引き換えに
君の解放を要求している…
They are demanding your release in exchange for the lives of the passengers.
フフ なるほど
それで私に彼らを説得しろと?
I see.
And now you want me to convince them?
私の妻と娘が乗つているのでね…
My wife and daughter are riding on board, you see?
Manfred Beriam, the man with tons of power and money...
いつから家族愛の人に
なつたのかな?
When did you become all family-loving?
からかう気か 化け物…
Are you mocking me, monster?
フ フ 本音が出ましたな…
There are your true colors.
奴らに投降するよう説得しろ
ヒユ一イラフオレツ卜!
Convince them to give themselves up.
Huey Laforet, I will take good care of you.
悪いようにはしない
ご安心なさい…
彼らの計画は嘉えます…
You can take it easy.
Their plan will fail.
何だと ?
What do you mean?
レムレ一スが列車を占拠したのなら
If the Lemures have occupied the train, my daughter ought to be riding it as well.
そこには私の娘も乗つているはずだ…
She has vowed absolute loyalty to me.
娘は私に
絶対の忠誠を誓っている…
The fanatic, Chane Laforet?
娘… 狂信者
シヤ一ネラフオレツ 卜か…
彼らがしていることが私にとつて
If what they are doing proves to be nothing but false kindness to me...
あり力ヾた迷惑 このうえない事態に
なつたとするならば…
Chane, you wouldn't hesitate...
シャ一ネ
お前は迷わないはずだ…
んん? どうした シヤ一ネ…
What's the matter, Chane?
フツ… フツフツ フン
あのね あのね
So, so...
食堂車の人たちを…
Can't you kill all the people in the dining car for me?
皆殺しにしてくれないかな?
何?
What?
I will pay you accordingly, of course.
もちろん それなりの報馴は
お渡ししますよ
You will be able to have some pleasure,
あなたは自分の快楽を得る
私は身の安全を買う…
and I get to buy my own safety.
You... You're not a child, are you?
てめえ… 子供じやねえなあ?
飲み込みが早くて助かります-
I'm glad you understand quickly.
If you can kill all of the passengers...
乗客を全員 殺してくれるのでしたら…
I will pay you 200,000 dollars.
報酉州 と して20万 ド丿 し
Hmm, this is pointless.
フン 話にならねえ…
食堂車だけで
何人殺す必要がある?
Why do we only have to kill those in the dining car?
I don't like to be toyed around with for loose change.
そんなは欝皇ねでいいように
踊らされるのはゴメンだぜ
お前が金を払う保証もねえしなあ~
Besides, there's no guarantee you will pay.
I have tons of explosives stowed away on this train...
私は この列車に大量の
爆薬を積んでいます
二ユ一ヨ一クの丿しノラ一夕
ファ三リ一と 取引するためです
in order to make a deal with the Runorata family from New York.
They trust me.
私には信用がある…
もし あなたたちが
言うことを聞いてくれたなら
If you will do what I ask of you,
I will make a recommendation to the Runoratas to look kindly upon you.
あなたたちが丿しノラ一夕に
優遇されるよう
ロ添えして差し上げますよ?
都合が良すきねえか ?
It sounds a little too good to be true.
爆薬は余分に積んでぁります
I have excess explosives stowed away.
あなたたちが食堂車の人間を
始末したあとに
After you have taken care of the people in the dining car,
I will let those explode.
それを爆破させます…
列車はス卜ツ ブ
The train will stop, and then we will take the remainder of the explosives and escape.
その間に我々は
残りの爆薬を持つて逃走します
The incident will probably be blamed on those people in the black suits.
事件は あの黒服どもの仕業ってことに
なるんじゃないでしようか…
そんな爆弾があるんだったら
どうして自分でやらない?
If you have such explosives, why don't you do it yourself?
I have business with one of the corpses.
ある人の死体に
用がありましてね…
乱暴に吹つ飛ばすワケには
いかないのです
I can't go in with force myself.
ねえ お兄ちゃん
やつてくれるよね?
So, mister... You will do it for me, right?
お前… 俺に対するロのきき方を
わきまえてなかったようだな…
It seems you haven't learned how to talk to me after all...
Huh?
そんな余裕のある目を
されてみろよ…
Just look at that self-confident face of yours...
I just can't help but want to kill you!
いやでも殺したく
なつちまうじゃねえかつ !
なにィ~
いきなり壺われただァ一!?
What?! You were suddenly attacked?!
はい… 殴られて目覚めてみたら
もう娘はいませんでした
Yes... They hit me, and when I woke up, the girl was gone.
くつそ~~~
Shit!
ガンド一丿しだ !
Damn Gandors! It must've been them!
ガンド一ルの
連中の仕業に違いねえ!
あっ… お ちよっ… くつ
Eve-chan! Eve-chan!
イブちゃん イブちやん…
工レアンさん?
Mr. Elean?
イブちゃん
ぴっくりさせて ごめんね…
Eve-chan, sorry for startling you.
今回のことに
どんなお薯ぴをしたらいいのか
How can we make up for all that happened to you?!
もう自分としては穴があったら
入つて出てきたくないくらいだよ…
If there was a hole, I'd want to crawl in and never come out again!
Did you come to save me?
助けてくれたんですか?
ああ! そうするのが
義務だと思ってねえ!
Yes, I saw it as my duty toward you.
ありがとう…
Thank you.
イブちゃん! 自分たちは君にお礼を
言われる立場じゃないんだよ!
Eve-chan, you have no reason to thank us.
君カヾ さらわれたこともそうだし
お兄さんのことだつて…
You were kidnapped because of us...
And your brother...
ダラス兄さんの?
Dallas-niisan? Did you find out anything about my brother?!
兄のことを
何か ご存じなんですか?
It's a top secret even within our company, and I only know very little myself, but...
会社としては特秘事項だし
自分が分かつてるのも ほんの
わずかなことなんだけど…
お詫ぴを兼ねて教えるとね
Let me tell you to make up for everything...
君のお兄さんの失踪には
Apparently the Gandor family is involved in the disappearance of your brother.
ガンド一丿しファミリ一が
かかわつてるらしいよ
The Gandors...
ガン ド一ル…
マフイア屋さんですか?
Are they mafia?
Yeah...
連れていって下さい!
ええ?
Please take me there!
Eh?
お願いです !
I beg of you. Please take me to the Gandors!
私をガンド一ルさんの所へ
連れていって!
お願いします !
Please!
なァ一 三リアア~ 工二スってば
警察に4人を届けたのかなァ一
Hey, Miria.
I wonder if Ennis delivered those four to the police.
そのあと うまく
逃げられてるといいね!
I hope she was able to escape afterwards.
で‥ 彼女 何したかったんだろぅ?
I wonder what she wanted to do.
ん~~~… 家出とか?
Run away from home?
Run away from home? That might just be true, Miria!
家出かァ~ そうかもなァ
ミリアァ~~
But she really was strong, don't you think?!
それにしても ほんっっっと
強かつたよなァ~
強かつたねつ !
She was so strong!
強い女の人つて
力ツ コいいよなァ一 !
Strong women are so cool!
Tomoe Gozen was one of the few examples of a true female samurai warrior in all of Japanese history.
卜モ工ゴゼンつてやつだねつ !
Like Tomoe Gozen, right?
ところでアイザツクう一
By the way, Isaac...
何だい? ミリア~~
What's the matter, Miria?
Where are we going now?
私たち これからどこ行くの ?
んあ~~~… それなんだけどなぁ…
About that...
Even though we want to steal money from the mafia,
マフイアの金を盗むつていつても
あんまり でっかい組の金を盗ったら
if we steal it from too big a group, loads of people will come after us, so...
追い力てけてくる奴が多くなつて
大変だろ?
I thought of taking the money of a small group that isn't widely connected.
そんなら どこにも属していない
小さな組織を狙おうつて寸法さ !
情報によると この辺りじゃ
マルテイ一ジヨファミリ一ってとこと
Around here, apparently it's the Gandor and Martillo families that fall under that category.
ガンド一ルファミリ一つてとこが
そういう組織らしい!
おお一一つ !
そこでだ…
That's where it's at.
Let's go to the Gandor family's hideout first, since it's closer.
とりあえず こつから近いガンド一丿し
ファ三リ一のアジ卜に行こう!
まあ 今巳のところは
様子見ってとこで
So let's wrap it up for now.
Wrap it up, right?!
様子見つてとこだねつ !
なぁ~ このまま
それを運んだとしてもよお~
Even if we bring this to him like this,
ほんとに金もらえんのかぁ ?
do you really think he'll pay us?
We'll just have to trust him.
信じるしかねえだろ…
But Dallas...
だけどよ ダラス
スコツ卜 あっさり殺したの見たろ~?
you saw how he killed Scott without blinking an eye!
俺らも用が済んだら
消されちまうんじゃねえのか~?
Don't you think he'll do the same to us when we're done?
スコツ 卜のことは忘れろ…
Forget about Scott.
Relax.
安心しな… 奴らは
この酒を欲しがつてる…
Those guys want this liquor.
We'll just point a gun at it,
だつたら この酒に
銃を突きつけりやいい…
金を受け取つてからじゃねえと
渡さねえってな…
telling 'em we won't give it to them until after they pay us.
I see!
なるほどお~…
あの注射で
頭まで良くなつたんじゃね~?
Did you get smarter as well thanks to that injection?
はつはあ一ん 三リァ
Miria...
ありゃあれだ
きっと組織のウラ金だな…
They must be carrying the organization's bribe money.
ヮイロだね…
That's bribe money, right?
夜中に3人がかりで
大事そうに運ぷものつて…
What is something that is so carefully carried around by three people?
お金だね
だろお?
It's money, right?
Right?!
So there's only one thing to do:
なら やることはー つ
今 あの金を奪う !
to steal that money right now!
どうして?
Why?
今 運んでるんだぞ
明日行っても金庫は空っぽだぁ
They're carrying it now!
The safe will be empty tomorrow!
そつかあ一一つ !
アイザック あったまい一一!
I see! You're so smart, Isaac!
待てえ一一いっ !
Wait!
なにイ !?
What the?!
とお一一一っ!
うつ… 誰だ 貴様はつ !
Who the hell are you?!
ワケあって ラインバッハの
滝の中から生還した男…
The man who safely returned from the Reichenbach Falls,
I am Professor Moriarty!
モリア一テイ教授 !
Well, call me Jack the Ripper then...
ああ じやあ
切り裂きジヤックでいいや
You making fools of us?!
なめてんのか コラア !
てめえみてぇな野郎の相手をしてる
ヒマはねえんだ!
We have no time to deal with the likes of you!
Well, how about me then?
じやあ 私の相手はどう ?
What?
なにイ? ウウツ…
目があ…
待ちやがれ ! こらあ !
アイザツクさん…
Mr. Isaac...
He's useless.
使えない奴…
ノチ工ス丿
どう實る?
あ蝿フはアテノごならな‥…
What should I do? He won't be of any help.
If things go on like this, I won't be able to search for the other Immortal.
このままさは ほヵの不死者き
探 實こ とがさきな! '
I accidentally introduced myself with my real name that time.
ぁの畦
! ' つの晨タノごヵ本名 き
名乗っごレまっご‥庭…
That means there must have been an Immortal in that room.
…ということは あの壕に
不死者ヵ!嘘ということ盧抑
I won't let them eat me!
食ゎれてたまるか…
I will have to eat them first!
先に食つてやらなければ…
あいつ さっき
死ななかつたつけか?
Didn't he die just a few minutes ago?
あ一 こんにちは一
Ohh, good day.
あなた確か 新聞社の人ですよね一
You were someone from the newspaper company, right?
ど どぅも
H-Hey there.
いいでしよ一
たくさん買つたんだぁ !
Aren't these nice?
I bought a lot!
良く切れるよ~~
They cut well!
おや…
Oh?
あなたは確ガ 新聞社の…
Aren't you... from the newspaper?
ど どうも‥
H-Hello.
一体 何事ですか ?
What's going on here?
いや… 実は…
Well... Truthfully...
ガン ド一ルさんですか?
Are you Mr. Gandor?
そうですが…
Yes?
私はイブ ジ工 ノ ア一 ドといいます
My name is Eve Genoard.
I am Dallas Genoard's younger sister.
ジ工ノア一ド…
Genoard...
ダラスつて あのクソガキか !
That shitty brat Dallas?!
兄のことを ご存じなんですね?
You know about my brother, right?
捜してるんです
I'm looking for him.
教えて下さい
兄カヾどこにいるのか!
Please tell me where he is!
どうしても知りたいのですか?
Do you really want to know?
仕方ないですね…
It can't be helped.
Gandor!
ガン ド一ルウ ウ ウ !
捜さなきゃ
ええ?
We have to look for them.
二一スと二ックは屋根から
食堂車の向こうへ行って
Nice and Nick, you two go over the roof to the other side of the dining car.
ド二一は僕と
うむ
You're with me, Donny.
二一ス… 絶対に戻ってくるから
無理しないで…
Nice, we'll definitely come back, so don't do anything crazy.
お熱いこってスねぇ 鯉さん…
You two sure are hot for each other, eh, Sis?
今のが初めてです…
はぁ?
Just now... was the first time!
The first time?! You have to be joking!
初めてつて そんな~
You and Jacuzzi have been dating for 10 years already, right?!
姐さんとジャグジ一は
付き合って もうー0年でしよ一一つ !
なのにキスー つもォ~!?
きやっ…
Without even one kiss?!
そおりやジヤグジ一
臆病にも ほどがありすきでしよ蝿
You can be too much of a coward, Jacuzzi!
姐さんも姐さんっスよォ一!
But you're to blame too, Sis!
But hey... Why did you kill him, Ladd?
だけどよ一 何で殺したんだよ ラッド
いい話だったじゃねえか
It sounded like a good deal to me.
確かになぁ… だがよお
あいつの目を見たか?
It sure did,
but did you see his eyes?
絶対に自分は殺されないつて
ツラしやがってよぉ
It was as if he just couldn't be killed or something.
He was sure that he couldn't be killed by us.
奴は俺たちになんか殺さねないって
確信してやがった!
このラッ ド丿しツソ様を
なめてくれやがったんだぜ!
He sure underestimated me!
My murderous gauge was turned to the max!
なんつ一か
殺意グ一ジMAXつて感じよ!
That's no reason to—
だからってよお一
But something just felt wrong...
しつかし気にくゎねえ !
最後の最後まで あいつは
余裕の表情を浮かベてやがった!
He had that self-confident look right until the very end.
何だつてんだ チクシヨ ウめ !
What was up with that?!
お~~い !
Hey!
うあ~~? うるしや一い !
Shut up!
見てみろよ
Take a look!
マズいですね…
This is bad.
スキがない…
There's no way to get past her.
ほーーう‥
新たな犠牲者発見つて感じイ一一?
Looks like I found myself a new bit of prey!
ノヒユ 一イ丿
河きレご!!る シヤ一ネ…
What are you doing, Chane?
ピシヤ一ネ丿
日互友潅ちな ここき運っご
蒻っごくるかもレカな‥
The white-clothed people might break through here and attack us.
ノヒユ 一イ丿
罵ヵなグ一ス庭ちき
守っごやるフも りヵ…
Are you going to protect that fool Goose and his underlings?
連中峡 お蔚き殺すフも り左ぞ
They are planning to kill you, you know.
I know.
{シヤ一ネ丿
分ヵフご〔!ます
あな潅き奪還誓き力ば
私は用済みノごなる…
As long as they can get their hands on you, they won't need me anymore.
彼ら凌泌要なのぽ
ぁくま 誓も 不死'の椰密
What they really want is the secret to immortality.
彼らの目的は
自分盧ちヵ不死者ノごなること…
Their goal is to become immortal themselves.
私もぁな潅も本すは彼らにご フ ご
どう誓も‥‥こと…
In truth, they really don't care about us.
ノヒユ 一イ丿
貰‥な シヤ一ネ…
You're a smart girl, Chane.
ノシヤ一ネ丿
あな盧から授ヵっ庭却識き守る庭め
私は声きなくレ庭…
To protect the knowledge I received from you, I abandoned speech.
私はも う怖…
I'm not afraid anymore.
あな潅き薯おうと豆る者き怨力な! !…
I don't fear those who want to take you from me.
Kヒユ 一イ丿
私き守っごくカるというのヵ」
シヤ一ネ…
Are you saying you will protect me, Chane?
ピシヤ一ネ丿
あな盧は不死者
あな盧は老! )なこ '
You are an Immortal. You don't age.
私 峡やヵご あな潅の年瞞き超え
I will grow older than you, and in the end, I will die before you.
やヵご あな盧より先ノご死ん さ乙 !く‥
ノプカ ど あな潅な私 き潅だ 7 入
愛レごくれる者…
However, you are the only one who loves me.
あな庭は私の盧だ7入の家族…
You are my only family,
だヵら あな潅き
奪ゎ力るゎけ仁は!)ヵな‥…
so I won't let you be taken from me.
誰仁も渡すゎけ仁峡! !ヵなC !…
I won't hand you over to anyone.
すげえな あの女 !
She's amazing! That woman!
へつ‥
よ一一一う!
この寒風吹きすさむ冬空に
Hey!
Aren't you cold in that skimpy dress with these damn cold winds?
そんなドレスで寒くねえのお一!?
The reason you guys were wearing such orchestra-style suits was...
お前らが そんな楽団の
格好してんのってよぉ
俺に演奏を
聴かせてくれるためだよなぁ!?
to perform for me, right?!
俺に ! 俺だけのために !
To think you'd come to the roof especially for me!
あんたは わざわざ屋根の上にまで
上カヾつてくれるとは!
とお一つ !
これは もはや愛だ一一一っ !
This must be love!
受け止めたぜぇ~~
お前の巨大な愛を!
I have embraced your enormous love!
今度は お前が俺の愛を
受け止めてくれ!
Now it's your turn to embrace my love.
I love you,
愛してるぜえ一一つつ !
so die!
だから死ねつ !
Is this for real?!
マジかよ
Is this for real? This just can't be!
おいおい
マジかよ おい !
ありえね一一つて
うりやあ !
This is my revenge. My revenge, you bastard!
お返しだよ… お返しだよ
お返しだよ バ力野郎!
Are you mortified? Do you want to die?
屈辱かい? 死にたいガい?
死にたくなくつても…
殺してやるがね!
Even if you don't want to die, I will still kill you!
You can't be serious!
マジかよ オイオイ マジかよ !
You can't be serious?!
マジイ!?
No way!
ありえねぇ一つて
ありえねえ一一つてえ !
This can't be...
This can't be!
フンツ !
フヒヤヒヤヒヤヒヤヒヤ
おおっとお!
あいつら化け物だ…
They are monsters!
Hey, looks like you snuck around long enough.
よお~~ 随分長いこと
はいつくばつてたみたいだなァ~
両手を上げて
下りてきてもらえないかな?
Raise your hands and please come down.
うつ ? ラツクガン ド一ル…
Luck Gandor!
おやおや… 随分騒がしいことだ…
Well, well. You look tense.
お前 死んだはずじや…
I thought you were dead?
まあ いいじゃないですか
そんなことは…
Let's just forget about it.
そ そんなことつて…
Forget?
なるほど…
I see now...
さては 影武者でも
使いやがつたなァ一一!
You used a body double or something, eh?
どこまでも
汚ねえマネをしやがって!
Your bag of filthy tricks just doesn't go empty, does it?
汚いマネ ?
Filthy tricks?
イブジ工ノア一ドを
さらっただろうがァ !
You were the ones who kidnapped Eve Genoard, weren't you?!
さあ 心当たりがありませんが…
Now... I don't really know what you're talking about.
ふざけるなぁ
ネ夕はあ力ヾってんだ
Don't fool with me!
We got news about it!
ダラスのガキと
組んでやがつたんだろうがぁ
You've teamed up with that Dallas brat, haven't you?!
You're wrong!
違います !
ああ… イブちやん !
Eve-chan!
へツ  あれが何よ り の証拠だ !
Ha! That's all the proof we need.
随分 一方的ですねえ…
That's quite one-sided of you, don't you think?
ああ‥ ー方的だ‥
Yeah... It's one-sided indeed.
今度こそ分かつたかぁ !
Do you get it now?!
何度も言うが力のある者が勝つ…
I'll tell you again and again: those with power win!
それが この世のお亮てだ
That's the rule of this world!
な… 何じやこりやあ~~! ぬわ~~~ いつてええ
W-What's going on here?
ま… この世には こういう力や
掟もあるってことですよ…
It just means there's this kind of power and rules in the world as well.
んな! はうつ…
いてえ!
Leave!
困つたなあ~
This sure is a letdown...
困つたねえ~
Sure is a letdown...
まさか酒とはなア~
To think it was alcohol...
まさか酒とはねえ~
To think it was alcohol!
まつ そういう時は !
Well, In cases like these,
残る一方のマフイアを
アテにするしかないなア一!
guess we'll just have to bust the remaining mafia family!
We'll just plunder their money then!
奴らから金をぶんどつてやるさ !
This time we're gonna take care of the Martillo family!
今度はマルテイ一ジヨ'ファミリ一に
様子見だねっ !
Martillo! Martillo! When I say Martillo, I mean Martillo!
ノアイザッ夕とミリア丿
マ丿!テイ一ジヨ ノ マ丿!テイ一ジヨノ
マ丿!テイ一ジヨっ左ら マ丿!テイ一ジヨノ
L\Lか 三 リア一
All right, Miria?
Let's behave naturally, like guests... Naturally.
客として自然に振る舞え…
自然にな…
うん ! 自然だね !
Yes! Naturally!
二ヒヒ ヒイ
ぬお~
神の おぼし召しがあらんことを…
We pray God's will is with you.
Haven't seen you before...
初顔だね… んん ?
丸にすんなつ !
Pay it no heed!
No heed!
すんなつ !
来な…
Follow me.
神の おぼし召しがあらんことを~~
We pray God's will is with you.
いらつしや一い !
Welcome!
Y-Yeah...
Lま !まあ‥
いいか… ここのどこかに
事務所があるらしい…
Listen carefully, somewhere around here is their office.
There should be a safe as well when we find it.
そこに行けば金庫もあるはずだ…
分かつたよ…
Got it!
Oh, and let's behave naturally like guests, naturally...
それと客として自然に振る舞え
自然にな…
うん 自然だね…
Yeah, naturally!
おう
おう !
うんしよ うんしよ
やつ ぱ り 事務所は地下だ !
Their office is down there, like I thought.
あ一一!
お客さん そこダメ一つ !
Ahh! Customers can't go there!
あん?
危ないヨ一一
早くどいて どいてぇええええっ !
It's dangerous!
Quickly get out of there!
どゎつ おぼし召しイ~~!?
Will of the heavens...
Celebrating the appointment of our new executive, let me fire a salute!
新しい幹部の誕生を祝って
私はここに祝砲を撃とう
おお一一つ
あはあ はぁはぁ はあん!
アイザツクが殺されたああああ !
Isaac was killed!
お客さんがちよ つ と大変ネ !
One of the guests is in a bit of a pinch.
おお一
うわああああああん
アイザックう一一!
Isaac!
泣くなぁ 三リア一!
まだ生きてるしィ一一!
Don't cry, Miria! I'm still alive...
But, but, but... You'll die, right?
でもでもでも
死んじゃうんでしよ一一?
まあ… いつかはな…
Well, at some point, yes.
うわああああん!
アイザックう~~!
Isaac!
Miria!
Aren't you the ones we met at the hatter's this afternoon?
あんたたち 昼間 帽子屋にいた…
ああ あの時の!
Ah! The people from that time!
すれ違つた人だね !
The people we passed by, right?
あんたたち…
I didn't know you two were a Father and a Sister!
フア一ザ一と
シス夕一だつたのかつ !
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Chane Laforet Remains Silent
in the Face of Two Mysterious People
Hey Miria, I think they mean us with those
"two mysterious people."
We silenced her, didn't we?
We sure did something inexcusable all of a sudden.
Indeed we did!
Even though we don't even know Ms. Chane...
Even though we didn't even meet her...